I don't know who made this, but I just received this from my sister and says they hate women so much they set up women for this moment to take their fall.
And if that isn't the damn truth, like they have put all these women in positions and they're just like pull my string and they repeat what he tells them to repeat and they will take the fall.
Just like Ghislaine has the only one who has taken the fall.
White women, white women, white women.
And at what point do y'all admit that you have agency?
When do you actually stop being a victim?
Because I want you to know there are only victims and volunteers.
And I got to tell you, y'all be volunteering all the goddamn time.
At what point?
Because I really feel like it's always, well, I had no choice.
Even much of me too was, well, I had no choice.
I had to sleep with him because they were going to fire me if I didn't.
I had to sleep with him because they said they wouldn't give me a promotion if I didn't.
At what point?
Because I want you to know that that is not grape.
That was an absolutely heinous situation that you were put in, but you chose to go along with it.
At no threat of your life.
At no threat of your family's life.
At threat of your advancement.
That is what all of those women are doing this for.
When these men present me with this carrot, I don't have to take it.
Because it's the same white women who will say, well, I had to beat the slaves.
Because my husband was sleeping with them.
So I had no choice but to discipline them.
Because I was upset that he was sleeping with them and not me.
And I was just in the house.
That's what y'all sound like.
Amen.